Guide to the Morris Edward Opler papers, [ca. 1960-1996]
Opler, Morris Edward papers, [ca. 1960-1996]
- Series I: Apache Indian Tribe
  - Subseries A: Research Items
    - Staa-Stank Journal Articles, 1949-1961 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Stanl Journal Articles (#1), 1952-1961 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Stanl Journal Articles (#2), 1963-1969 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Stanl Journal Articles (#3), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Stanm-Stec Journal Articles, 1889-1972 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Steck Papers from the University of New Mexico, 1853-1855 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Steck Papers (#1), 1841 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Steck Papers (#2), 1855 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Steck Papers (#3), 1856 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Steck Papers (#4), 1857-1858 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Steck Papers (#5), 1858-1859 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Steck Papers (#6), 1859-1961 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Steck Papers (#7), 1862-1863 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Steck Papers (#8), 1864 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Steck Papers (#9), 1865 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Steck Papers (#10), 1866 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Sted-Stev Journal Articles, 1879-1939 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Stew-Sto Journal Articles, 1897-1994 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Str-Sty Journal Articles, 1924-1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Su-Sy Journal Articles, 1916-1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Ta Journal Articles, 1862-1982 (I) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Ta Journal Articles, 1862-1982 (II) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Te Journal Articles, 1847-1962 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Tha-Thol Journal Articles, 1931-1970 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Thom Journal Articles (#1), 1928-1933 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Thom Journal Articles (#2), 1940 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Thom Journal Articles (#3), 1899-1972 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Thon-Thy Journal Articles, 1879-1978 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Ti-To Journal Articles, 1908-1941 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Tr-Tu Journal Articles, 1907-1975 (I) (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Tr-Tu Journal Articles, 1907-1975 (II) (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Trennert, R.A., "The Far Western Indian Frontier..." Thesis, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Twitchell, R.E., "The Leading Facts of New Mexican History," Parts I and II, 1911 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Twitchell, R.E., "The Leading Facts of New Mexican History," Part III, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Twitchell, R.E., "The Leading Facts of New Mexican History," Parts IV and V, 1917 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Tw Journal Articles, 1909-1968 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Ty Journal Articles, 1958-1968 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Tyler, Barbara A. "Apache Warfare under the Leadership of Cochise", 1965 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Ua-Uz Journal Articles, 1947-1973 (I) (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Ua-Uz Journal Articles, 1947-1973 (II) (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Miscellaneous and Annual Reports, 1869-1874 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports, 1892-1949 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#1), 1850-1854 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#2), 1855-1858 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#3), 1859 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#4), 1860-1864 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#5), 1865-1867 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#6), 1868-1869 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#7), 1870-1871 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#8), 1872-1874 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#9), 1875-1879 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#10), 1880-1884 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports(#11), 1885-1889 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#12), 1890-1891 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#13), 1892-1894 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#14), 1895-1899 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#15), 1900-1904 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#16), 1875-1889 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#17), 1890-1919 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#18), 1919-1932 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Government Bureau of Indian Affairs, 1968-1970 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#19), 1905-1909 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#20), 1910-1914 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#21), 1915-1919 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#22), 1920-1929 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#23), 1930-1939 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - U.S. Government Board of Indian Commissioners Annual Reports (#24), 1940-1954 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - U.S. Government Congress-House of Representatives Committee on Indian Affairs, 1923-1939 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Government Congress-House of Representatives Committee on Public Lands, 1950 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Government Congress-House of Representatives Documents (29th-34th Congress), 1847-1854 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - U.S. Government Congress-House of Representatives (35th-38th Congress), 1857-1860 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Government Congress-House of Representatives (39th-43rd Congress), 1866-1875 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - U.S. Government Congress-House of Representatives (44th-48th Congress), 1876-1881 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - U.S. Government Congress-House of Representatives (49th Congress), 1887 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - U.S. Government Congress-House of Representatives Reports, 1914 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - U.S. Government Congress-Joint Special Committee ("Condition of Indian Tribes"), 1867 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Government Congress-Senate Committee on Indian Affairs, 1931-1939 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - U.S. Government Congress-Senate Documents (32nd-50th Congress), 1851-1887 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - U.S. Government Congress-Senate Documents (51st-72nd Congress), 1890-1932 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - U.S. Government Congress-Senate Reports, 1895 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - U.S. Government Court of Claims, 1897 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - U.S. Government Executive Orders, 1909 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - U.S. Government Federal Writers' Project, 1937-1939 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - U.S. Government General Land Office, 1865-1890 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - U.S. Government Indian Claims Commission, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - U.S. Government-Department of Interior, 1894-1898 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - U.S. Government National Archives, 1885-1890 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - U.S. Government National Park Service, 1963-1976 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - U.S. Government-U.S. Army, 1870-1878 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Government War Department, 1857-1933 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Government Secretary of War, 1850-1886 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Vaa-Vam Journal Articles, 1850-1971 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Van-Vaz Journal Articles, 1866-1945 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Van Valkenburgh, Richard F. Papers, 1890 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Ve Journal Articles, 1861-1948 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Vi Journal Articles, 1955-1970 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Vo-Vy Journal Articles, 1933-1970 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Waa-Walk Journal Articles, 1937-1975 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Wall Journal Articles (#1), 1951-1965 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Wall Journal Articles (#2), 1943-1958 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Walm-Wea Journal Articles, 1858-1976 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Web Journal Articles (#1), 1922-1952 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Web Journal Articles (#2), 1913-1971 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Wec-Wedd Journal Articles, 1964-1968 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Wede Journal Articles, 1940-1972 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Wede Journal Articles, 1950-1976 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Wedf-Well Journal Articles, 1927-1954 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Wellman, Paul, "The Indian of the West", 1947 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Welm-Wem Journal Articles, 1887-1979 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Wen-Wez Journal Articles, 1905-1955 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Wha-Whe Journal Articles, 1902-1969 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Whia-Whis Journal Articles, 1856-1965 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Whit-Why Journal Articles, 1873-1971 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Wia-Wilk Journal Articles, 1938-1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Will-Wilr Journal Articles, 1899-1956 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Wils-Wim Journal Articles, 1896-1979 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Win-Wiz Journal Articles, 1896-1973 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Winfrey and Day "The Indian Papers of Texas and the Southwest," Vol. I and II, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Winfrey and Day "The Indian Papers of Texas and the Southwest," Vol. III, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Winfrey and Day "The Indian Papers of Texas and the Southwest," Vol. IV and V, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Woa-Wook Journal Articles, 1906-1962 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Wool-Worl Journal Articles, 1898-1975 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Worm-Wre Journal Articles, 1955-1971 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Wri-Wyl Journal Articles, 1908-1961 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Wym Journal Articles (#1), 1936-1943 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Wym Journal Articles (#2), 1944-1959 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Wm Journal Articles, 1932-1972 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Wyn-X Journal Articles, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Ya-Yot Journal Articles, 1856-1951 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - You-Yu Journal Articles, 1944-1961 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Z Journal Articles, 1944-1959 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Aa-Ag Reprint Journal Articles (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Ah-Ak Reprint Journal Articles (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Al Reprint Journal Articles (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Am-Ar Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Asa-Asg Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Ash Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Asi-Az Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Baa-Barna Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Barne Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Barni-Barz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Bat-Beb Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Bas Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Bec-Bel Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Bem-Benm Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Benn-Benz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Beo-Bez Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Bh-Bis Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Bit-Bl Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Boa(#1) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Boa(#2) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Boa(#3) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Bob-Bram Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Bran-Brij Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Brik-Bro Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Bru-By Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Caa-Cas Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Cat-Cha Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Che-Cog Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - Coh Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Coi-Col Reprint Journal Articles (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Com-Coo Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Cop-Cy Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Da-Dej Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Dek-Det Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Deu-Dez Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Doc-Doq Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Dor-Doz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Dr-Dy Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Ea-Eg Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Eh-El Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Em-Ez Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Fa-Fen Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Feo-Fla Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Fle-Fo Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Fra-Fre Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Fri-Fy Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Ga Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Ge-Gik Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Gila-Gill Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Gilm-Golc Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Gold-Golz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Gom-Goz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Gr-Gy Reprint Journal Articles (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Haa-Hak Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Hala-Halln Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Hallo Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Halm-Haro Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Harp-Haz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Hea-Herr Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Hers(#1) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Hers(#2) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Hers(#3) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Hert-Hill Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Hilm-Hiz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Hoa-Hod Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Hoe-Hoh Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Hoi-Hok Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Hol-Hoo Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Hop-Hov Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - How-Hoz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Hra-Huk Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Hul-Hy Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - I Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Ja-Je Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Ji-Jy Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Kaa-Kaq Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Kar-Kaz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Ke-Kh Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Ki-Klo Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Klu(#1) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Klu(#2) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Klu(#3) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Klu(#4) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Kn-Krod Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Kroe(#1) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Kroe(#2) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Kroe(#3) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Krof-Ky Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Laa-Lam Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Lan-Leg Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Leh-Lek Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Lel-Les Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Let-Lez Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Lia-Lio Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Lip-Ll Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Loa-Lov Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Low(#1) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Low(#2) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Lox-Lyz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Maa-Mac Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Mad-Malh Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Mali-Manc Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Mand(#1) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Mand(#2) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Mane-Mar Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Masa-Masn Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Maso Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Masp-Mau Reprint Journal Articles (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Mav-Mc Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Mea Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Meb-Meq Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Mer Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Mes-Mik Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Mil-Moo Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Mop-Mov Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Mow-Moz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Mu-My Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Naa-Nas Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Nat-Naz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Ne-Ni Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - No-Ny Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Oa-Oo Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Op-Oq Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Or-Oz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Paa-Parr Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Pars Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Part-Paz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Pe-Pi Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Pl-Po Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Pr-Py Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Q Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Raa-Rah Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Rai-Raz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Rea-Reh Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Rei-Rez Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Ri-Rog Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Roh-Roz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Ru-Ry Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Saa-Sao Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Sap(#1) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Sap (#2) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Sap (#3) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Saq-Sar Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Sas-Schm Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Schn-Schy Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Sea-Shap Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Shar-Shy Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Si Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Sj-Sm Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Sn-Sph Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Spi Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Spl-Sr Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Sta-Stev Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Stew(#1) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Stew(#2) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Stew(#3) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Stex-Sti Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Sto-Stra Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Stre-Stu Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Sty-Sy Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Ta Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Te-Thol Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Thom Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Thon-Thy Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Ti Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - To-Tul Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Tum-Ty Reprint Journal Articles (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - U Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Vi Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Va-Ve Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Voa-Voe Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Vof-Vy Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Waa-Waq Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - War-Waz Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - We-Whe Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Whi(#1) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Whi(#2) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Whi(#3) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - Who-Wil Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - Wim-Wis Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Wit(#1) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Wit(#2) Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Wo-Wr Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Wu-Wy Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Z Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - X,Y Reprint Journal Articles (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Articles and Materials from Specific Places of Research
      - Arizona: Arizona Historical Society (Tuscon, Ariz.) (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Arizona: Museum of Northern Arizona and No. Arizona University (Flagstaff, Ariz.) (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Arizona: University of Arizona (Tucson, Ariz.) (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - California: Huntington Library and Art Gallery (San Marino, Calif.) (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - California: Southwest Museum (Los Angeles, Calif.) (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - California: University of California (Berkeley, Calif.) (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - California: University of Southern Calif. (Los Angeles, Calif.) (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - New Mexico: Alamorgordo (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - New Mexico: Laboratory of Anthropology (Santa Fe, N.M.) (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - New Mexico: Museum of Navajo Ceremonial (Santa Fe, N.M.) (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - New Mexico: Museum of New Mexico (Santa Fe, N.M.) (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - New Mexico: University of New Mexico (Albuquerque, N.M.) (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Oklahoma: Fort Sill Museum (U.S. Army Artillery and Missile Center Museum, Fort Sill, OK) (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Oklahoma: Oklahoma Historical Society (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Oklahoma: University of Oklahoma (Norman, OK) (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Oklahoma: Thomas Gilcrease Institute of American History and Art (Tulsa, OK) (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Oklahoma: Philbrook Art Center (Tulsa, OK) (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Pennsylvania: American Philosophical Society (Philadelphia, PA) (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Texas: Baylor University (Waco, TX) (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Texas: Southern Methodist University (Dallas, TX) (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Texas: Texas Christian University (Fort Worth, TX) (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Texas: Texas State Archives (Austin, TX) (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Texas: Texas Tech University (Lubbock, TX) (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Texas: University of Texas (Austin, TX) (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Texas: West Texas State University (Canyon, TX) (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Utah: University of Utah (Salt Lake City, UT) (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Washington, DC: Anthropological Archives (Smithsonian) (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Washington, DC: U.S. National Archives (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Subseries B: Chiricahua
    - Manuscript notes for Chiricahua-alien people (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Photographs of Apache dress (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Chiricahua Bands-history and location, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Chiricahua Biography (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Chiricahua Bands (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Chiricahua Biography (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Chiricahua Biography (Charlie Smith) (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Chiricahua Biography (Charlie Smith) (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Chiricahua Biography (Charlie Smith) (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Chiricahua Biography (Charlie Smith) (Box 35, Folder 10)